Agustin Bautista

Contact: abautist703@gmail.com 206-747-3198

Online: LinkedIn Website

Profile

Recently relocated to New York, I am a strong front-end web developer with an eye for design. Fully competent building full stack web applications with experience using node.js and ruby on rails. Organized, detail-oriented and with international account management experience, I stay on top of deadlines and prioritize work decisively.

Experience

Web Development Teaching Assistant, General Assembly

Seattle, WA - Jan 2016-Apr 2016

Regular interaction with 15+ students, guiding instruction on various web development topics, debugging and communicating coding best practices. Provide assistance on several projects built in various languages and frameworks including node.js and ruby on rails

Web Development Immersive, General Assembly

Seattle, WA - Sep 2015-Dec 2015

12-week program covers HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, node.js, express.js, PostgreSQL, Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, and other technologies

Organic Farmer, Jumanji Farm

Sno-Valley and Seattle, WA - May 2014-Dec 2015

Founded and managed small-scale mixed vegetable farm as a participant of Sno-Valley Tilth's Experience Farming Project. Sold organic produce through a CSA subscription service and farmers markets in Seattle.

Senior Associate, Ogilvy Financial | Ogilvy Public Relations

Beijing and Singapore - Aug 2009-Dec 2012

Supported communications and investor relations programs for various China-based US-listed companies. Responsibilities included account management, planning, strategy, and media outreach

Education

General Assembly; Seattle, WA - web development immersive, 2015 Hamilton College; Clinton, NY – B.A. cum laude, Chinese studies, 2008

Skills

Responsive Web Design | HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass | JavaScript | jQuery | Express.js | Node.js | Ruby on Rails | Bootstrap | PostgreSQL | MongoDB | Git | AngularJS | React | ES2015

References

Brian Hague, General Assembly Web Developer, Instructor — <u>brian.hague@ga.co</u>
Josh Sera, General Assembly Mobile Developer, Instructor — <u>josh.sera@ga.co</u>
Annie Ly, General Assembly Instructional Designer — <u>annie.ly@generalassemb.ly</u>